I won't let anything happen to you.
You're awake.
I think I...
had a dream.
I'm sorry.
I failed to protect you.
It will never happen again.
Miao Miao, you're awake!
You scared me to death, do you know that?
Sis.
You don't know how worried I was about you.
I thought I'd never see you again.
Don't worry.
I'm still your one and only sister.
Sis, are you feeling better now?
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Come, come, come.
Have a seat.
Drink some pomelo water.
May it bless you to turn misfortune into fortune from now on.
So simple.
Since when did you become so superstitious?
Superstition? Nonsense.
Kids like you don't understand.
Dear gods, please don't mind her ignorance.
Please bless her with safety and peace.
Safety and peace, safety and peace.
Sis.
You should be thanking my brother-in-law instead.
Exactly, exactly!
Come, come, our great hero.
Sit, please have a seat.
I'll go prepare a big meal for you all!
Hey, Ayi Te.
Why are you just standing there?
Come and help!
Alright.
Let's go, let's go.
I'll come too!
Are you feeling okay?
Are you sure saving me won't affect you?
No, it won't.
Besides,
didn't your kiss replenish my energy?
Come over here.
Hao Ruichi.
Hao Ruichi, what's wrong? Hao Ruichi!
Simple.
Ai Yite.
Still no signs of waking up?
It's been two days already.
My sister hasn't had a drop of water.
Ai Yite.
Step outside for a moment.
I need to ask you something.
Ai Yite.
Is Hao Ruichi in this state because he saved me?
He...
...gave you his life energy.
Is there any way to save him?
His body was already weak on this star.
Now that he's out of energy, I'm afraid...
...I'm afraid his chances are slim.
Ai Yite, please tell me how I can save him!
I'll do anything.
I'm begging you, Ai Yite.
If you want to save him...
...you must send him back.
Then...
...how do we send him back?
When I came here...
...the spaceship fell into the water.
It's not damaged.
The kitchen work is done.
Take a break after you’re done.
I'll watch the shop for a while.
Go ahead and bring some food to Miaomiao and the others.
Here...
...are all my cooking notes.
And...
...all the cooking steps.
Idiot.
My cooking is already so delicious,
...why would I need this?
When making seafood noodles in the future...
...remember to use less seasoning.
Otherwise, it will ruin the seafood's flavor.
And when washing dishes...
...remember to wear gloves.
It's getting cold.
Just use hot water.
And when there's no one around at night,
close the store a bit earlier.
The most, most, most important thing is,
next time you hire someone,
don’t trust people so easily.
Ayet,
you will come back, right?
Of course.
Blue Star can't hold me.
I will definitely come back.
Alright.
Then I'll wait for you.
If you're late coming back, you're so dead.
Hao Ruichi,
you're going back.
Get better soon.
Miao Miao,
it's time.
Let's go.
Don't worry,
he's going to be fine.
What's wrong?
He doesn’t seem to have a pulse.
Hao Ruichi!
Wake up!
You’re joking, right?
No, no way.
Hao Ruichi, wake up!
You can't do this.
Stop joking with me!
Didn’t you say,
didn’t you say you’d stay with me?
Hao Ruichi, wake up for me!